I said this the other day, again, people can say what they want on the sidewalk, and we respect that.
That's what the First Amendment's about.
But this word genocide's getting thrown around in a pretty inappropriate way by lots of different folks.
What Hamas wants, make no mistake about it, is genocide.
First of all, the reality is that even if Hamas wanted genocide, they are incapable of achieving it.
However, you know who is? Israel.
Israel is capable of achieving a genocide.
They're literally in the process of doing it right now.
If you look at the actual numbers of people in Israel who have been harmed by Hamas,
and at the numbers of people in Palestine who have been harmed by Israel,
the numbers are so disproportionately staggering.
It is like Hamas is a ragtag band of ruffians.
It's like literally they're led by Rufio.
Like that's how it looks on paper.
Furthermore, whatever you feel about Hamas, their charter does not say that they want to eradicate Jewish people.
What it does say is that they want to get rid of Israel.
And that is not doing so in necessarily a violent fashion.
It is simply the undoing of the settler state of Israel as an occupier of Palestine.
The continued misrepresentation of that is rhetoric meant to support the idea that Israelis deserve to exist in place of Palestinians in Palestine.
And ultimately, when he's talking all messy like that, that shows that they actually do not want peace.